<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.2" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.2" modifiedDate="2025-04-17T16:10:31">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>A Jego imie Jezus</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Jeremy Riddle</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1a">
      <lines>Jedynie On odkupieniem jest<br/>Jedynie On przezwyciężył śmierć<br/>There's only One who overcame the grave<br/>There's only One strong enough to save</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1b">
      <lines>Jedynie On jest godzien przyjąć cześć<br/>There's only One who's worthy of all praise</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2a">
      <lines>W ręku ma klucz do piekła bram<br/>A Jego głos uzdrawia każdą z ran<br/>And in His hands, the keys of death and hell<br/>And in His name, a power that can heal</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2b">
      <lines>On swoją krwią z grzechów obmył nas<br/>And by His blood, our sins are washed away</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>A Jego imię: Jezus<br/>Jego imię: Jezus<br/>Jego imię: Królów Król<br/>Doradca nasz, Wszechmocny Bóg<br/>His name is Jesus<br/>His name is Wonderful<br/>Counselor, Almighty God!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3a">
      <lines>Niech każdy z nas chwałę odda Mu<br/>Niech cały świat padnie Mu do stóp<br/>Nations kneel<br/>And glorify the Lord!<br/>Let all the earth<br/>Tremble for He comes!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3b">
      <lines>Nadchodzi sąd, a Sędzią jest nasz Bóg<br/>And He will judge the living and the dead!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4a">
      <lines>Człowieczy Syn przyjdzie w chwale swej<br/>Na odgłos trąb każdy skłoni się<br/><br/>The Son of Man coming on the clouds<br/>With trumpet sound and every knee will bow</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4b">
      <lines>I wyzna to: On wielkim Bogiem jest<br/>And tongue confess the Name above all names!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="b1a">
      <lines>To Doradca nasz<br/>Pełen mocy Bóg<br/>To pokoju Pan<br/>HE IS COUNSELOR!<br/>HE IS MIGHTY GOD!<br/>HE'S THE PRINCE OF PEACE!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="b1b">
      <lines>Wszechpotężny Król<br/>On cudowny jest<br/>Piękny w chwale swej<br/>Wszechmocny Bóg<br/>THE OMNIPOTENT!<br/>HE IS WONDERFUL!<br/>HE IS RADIANT!<br/>THE ALMIGHTY GOD!</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
