<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.2" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.2" modifiedDate="2025-04-17T16:10:57">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Jireh</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Maverick City Music</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1a">
      <lines/>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1b">
      <lines>I'll never be more loved than I am right now<br/>Wasn't holding You up<br/>So there's nothing I can do to let You down<br/>It doesn't take a trophy to make You proud<br/>I'll never be more loved than I am right now, oh</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1c">
      <lines>Going through a storm but I won't go down<br/>I hear Your voice<br/>Carried in the rhythm of the wind to call me out<br/>You would cross an ocean so I wouldn't drown<br/>You've never been closer than You are right now</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1d">
      <lines>Jirah, you are enough<br/>Jirah, you are enough<br/>And I will be content<br/>in every circumstance<br/>Jirah, you are enough.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1e">
      <lines>Forever enough, always enough, more than enough</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1f">
      <lines>I don't wanna forget how I feel right now<br/>On the mountaintop<br/>I can see so clear what it's all about<br/>So stay by my side when the sun goes down<br/>Don't wanna forget how I feel right now</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1g">
      <lines>I'm already loved, I'm already chosen<br/>I know who I am, I know what you've spoken<br/>I'm already loved, more thank I can imagine<br/>And that is enough, that is enough.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1h">
      <lines>If he dresses the Lilies, <br/>With beauty and splendour<br/>how much more will he clothe you x2<br/>If he watches over, every sparrow,<br/>How much more will he love you x2</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1i">
      <lines>More than you ask, think or imagine<br/>According to His power<br/>Working in us<br/>it's more than enough</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
