<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.2" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.2" modifiedDate="2025-04-17T16:11:06">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Philip Saturday Gospel ENG</title>
    </titles>
    <authors>
      <author>Author Unknown</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>When a large crowd gathered, with people from one town after another<br/>journeying to Jesus, he spoke in a parable.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>"A sower went out to sow his seed.<br/>And as he sowed, some seed fell on the path and was trampled,<br/>and the birds of the sky ate it up.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Some seed fell on rocky ground, and when it grew,<br/>it withered for lack of moisture.<br/>Some seed fell among thorns,<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>and the thorns grew with it and choked it.<br/>And some seed fell on good soil, and when it grew,<br/>it produced fruit a hundredfold."<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>After saying this, he called out,<br/>"Whoever has ears to hear ought to hear."<br/>Then his disciples asked him<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>what the meaning of this parable might be.<br/>He answered,<br/>"Knowledge of the mysteries of the Kingdom of God<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>has been granted to you;<br/>but to the rest, they are made known through parables<br/>so that they may look but not see, and hear but not understand.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>"This is the meaning of the parable.<br/>The seed is the word of God.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>Those on the path are the ones who have heard,<br/>but the Devil comes and takes away the word from their hearts<br/>that they may not believe and be saved.<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>Those on rocky ground are the ones who, when they hear,<br/>receive the word with joy, but they have no root;<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>they believe only for a time and fall away in time of temptation.<br/>As for the seed that fell among thorns,<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines>they are the ones who have heard, but as they go along,<br/>they are choked by the anxieties and riches and pleasures of life,<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v13">
      <lines>and they fail to produce mature fruit.<br/>But as for the seed that fell on rich soil,<br/>they are the ones who, when they have heard the word,<br/></lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v14">
      <lines>embrace it with a generous and good heart,<br/>and bear fruit through perseverance."<br/></lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
